If only you were dead.
Keeper is a horror, mystery film directed by Osgood Perkins.
Liz and Malcolm escape for a romantic anniversary weekend at a secluded cabin.
When Malcolm suddenly returns to the city, Liz finds herself isolated and in the
presence of an unspeakable evil that reveals the cabin's horrifying secrets.
Liz / Ada, played by Tatiana Maslany.
Malcolm Westbridge, played by Rossif Sutherland.
Darren, played by Birkett Turton.
Minka, played by Eden Weiss.
Baghead, played by Cassandra Ebner.
Maggie / Baghead, played by Tess Degenstein.
Keeper is a 2025 folk horror film directed by Osgood
Perkins and written by Nick Lepard.
The film stars Tatiana Maslany, Rossif Sutherland,
Birkett Turton, and Eden Weiss.
Maslany and Sutherland are also two of the film's executive
and co-executive producers, respectively.
The film follows a couple spending their anniversary weekend at a secluded cabin in the woods,
where strange things begin occurring and the cabin's dark secrets are revealed.
Keeper was released in the United States on November 14, 2025 by
Neon, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of ritual, cake, woods, cabin, torture.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.